export const questions = [
    { question: '5 + 3', options: ['6', '7', '8', '9'], answer: '8' },
    { question: '12 - 4', options: ['6', '8', '9', '7'], answer: '8' },
    { question: '3 x 3', options: ['6', '9', '12', '8'], answer: '9' },
    { question: '16 / 4', options: ['3', '4', '5', '6'], answer: '4' },
    { question: '10 + 5', options: ['12', '15', '17', '14'], answer: '15' },
    { question: '7 - 2', options: ['5', '4', '6', '3'], answer: '5' },
    { question: '6 x 2', options: ['10', '11', '12', '13'], answer: '12' },
    { question: '15 / 3', options: ['4', '5', '6', '7'], answer: '5' },
    { question: '8 + 6', options: ['12', '14', '13', '15'], answer: '14' },
    { question: '9 - 3', options: ['5', '6', '7', '8'], answer: '6' }
];
